

Pavel Kvasnička

Profile

Results driven leader with experience in technically focused industries who thinks about issues in a broader context at a top management level. Enjoys surrounding and collaborating with capable people. Through individual motivation of subordinates and SMART tasks, he achieves set goals. A fair approach is a primary principle not only in professional life. He is not afraid of direct confrontation and uses logic and natural intelligence to find a solution to any problem.

Details

+420 606 651 284 pavelkvasnicka@gmail.com

Skills
people motivation
project managing
problem analysis and solution proposal
eye for detail

Previous employment

R&D, Technology and Project Manager, Dirac Industries

January 2020 – December 2021, January 2014 – December 2017

- Management of a department forming the core of the company's production program / know-how
- Recruiting, motivating and evaluating a team of engineers and technologists (6 subordinates, 1 shift operation)
- Assigning, controlling and evaluating tasks assigned to subordinates
- Setting departmental objectives in relation to the corporate strategy
- Working closely with the production and quality department
- Project management in new product development
- Reporting the results of the department to the CEO (CZ) and the owner of the company (BE)

Production Manager, Foxconn Technology

January 2018 – December 2019

- Starting a new project from an empty hall to a working production line
- Production and warehouse management
- Recruitment, motivation and evaluation of subordinates (100 subordinates in 3 levels, 2 shifts)
- Resolving operational situations to ensure the smooth running of the line
- Organizing human resources when production schedule changes
- Responsibility for compliance with internal regulations and employer's guidelines, HSE and SER principles
- Reporting production results to the Center Manager (CZ) and Branch Manager (IRL)

Project Manager, Beck&Pollitzer

January 2012 – December 2013

- Complete project management of relocations of production facilities and manufacturing companies throughout Europe
- Creation and evaluation of relocation contract budgets from pricing to invoicing
- Managing the implementation team both on site and remote depending on the scope of the job
- Managing a team of 5 20 subordinates (various technical professions)
- Direct communication with the customer throughout the implementation
- Reporting the results of orders to the branch manager (CZ)

■ Education

Commercial Electrical Engineering, University of West Bohemia in Pilsen

September 2005 – July 2010

Language skills

Czech - native speaker, English - advanced

Organizational skills and knowledge

Knowledge and experience in interpersonal communication, project management, time management